老天 迈克
Woman: Jesus, Michael.
你是想跟神龛聊聊吗
You want to Gram with the shrine?
不 不用了
Woman No Tm uh. I'm good.
凯瑟琳
Well, Kathleen.
-欢迎来到享乐生活 -行吧
Welcome to the life Kathleen: Mm- hmm
嗨 亲爱的
Hey, sweetheart
凯瑟林 这是我太太艾娃
Kathleen, I'd love for youi to meet my wife, Ava.
艾娃 这是我的宿敌
Ava, I'd like for you to meet my mortal enemy,
凯瑟琳·汤森
Kathleen Townsend.
凯瑟琳
Ava: Kathleen
很高兴终于能见到你了
It is a pleasure to finally meet you.
我也一样
Well, likewise. Likewise.
-恭喜啊 新婚夫妻 -谢谢你
Congratulations, newlyweds Michael and Ava: Thank you.
忘年恋总是让我觉得暖暖的
A May December romance really warms my heart.
你真是太好了
that's so sweet.
-而且你看上去好美 -谢谢你
And you look wonderful, by the way Thank you,
我记得这一套是第六季的衣服吧
I think I recognize that outfit from season six
好吧 那你们俩慢慢叙旧
Okay, well, I will leave the two of you to catch up.
Okay, well, Lwill leave the two of you to catch up.
表现好一点
Behave
恭喜你
Congratulations.
还不错啊
Not bad
一年前
Imean, a year ago,
你还在跟会说话的海狸
you were doing insurance commercials
拍保险广告
with talking beavers.
现在 你住这么大房子
And now, now you have all this
她是家里有矿吗
She have family money?
不 艾娃完全是靠自己
Oh no. Ava is 100%self- made
她创建了专属女性的在线折扣经纪
She founded a discount online brokerage for women
她之交易
She Trade.
所以这对我来说是相当享受了
So this is a treat,
你销声匿迹三年
After three years radio silence
怎么突然跑来了 赎罪的其中一步吗
What is this? Some kind of 12 Step thing?
你是在戒断愤怒吗 所以来补偿我的
You're a rage- a- holic? You here to make amends?
不是
No.
这对我来说并不容易 迈克
This isn't easy for me, Michael
我知道我们过去伤害过彼此
I know that we have hurt each other in the past.
我知道我把你伤得很重
I know that I have hurt you terribly.
但我需要请你帮个忙
But I have to ask you fora favor.
我希望你能跟我一起演一场戏
I want you to do a play with me.
笑什么 就一晚上在地方剧院
What? It's one night only. Regional theater.
但他们很有钱
Oh, but they have very deep pockets.
我觉得那边有些捐赠者是《幽灵》的狂热粉丝
I think some of the donors are big"Spooky"fans actually
他们的价钱开得很高
They offered big money.
什么戏
What's the play?
《彭萨科拉的幽灵》
"The Ghosts of Pensacola. "
听我说 就算是30年前 那玩意儿也是烂透的
Ugh. Listen, even 30 years ago, that mope- fest sucked.
那是我们职业生涯中得到的最高评价了
Those were the best reviews of our career.
那标准可太低了
It's a low bar.
迈克 你知不知道
Michael, do you know
如果你明天就死了
that if you died tomorrow,
那么留在大家心中的
you would be remembered
就是《幽灵与警察》里面的你
for Spooky and the Cop.
那真是好极了
Michael: Well, that's great.
说明我给很多人带去了快乐
That means I provided joy to a lot of people.
你是个艺肃家
You are an artist.
你是天生的艺市家
It rages in your blood.
我了解你的灵魂
I know your soul.
我记得你在舞台上的激情
I remember what the fire was like on that stage.
我觉得你太夸张了 亲爱的
Okay, I think you're overselling it, darling.
在我们成功之前
The primal connection we had
在我们闹翻和出丑闻之前
before the success,
我们所拥有的那种原始的联系
before the feuds and the tabloids.
是啊 你还在《人民》杂志的采访里
Oh yeah, and the "People" magazine interview
暗示我不认字呢
where you implied that I couldn't read.
我道过歉了
I said I was sorry.
我的维基有科上还有着一条
It's still on my Wikipedia page.
一整条条目 说我文盲
There's a whole subheading. "Illiteracy. "
迈克 我现在很绝望
Michael, Im desperate.
求你了 我真的求你了
Please, I'm begging you.
你要我做什么都可以
I will do anything you want.
让我公开下跪都可以
I will prostrate myself publicly.
但我真的很需要这一次
But I need this.
你知道业界对特定年纪的女演员来说是什么样的吗
Do you know what it's like for an actress of a certain age?
从演妈妈 到演参议院
You go from mom to senator
再到演痴呆患者
to dementia patient.
我真的很需要那笔钱
And, and I need the money.
And, and I need the money
那很抱歉 凯瑟琳 我还是拒绝
Well, I'msorry, Kathleen. The answer's no.
好吗
Okay.
但如果你需要现金的话 我可以 我可以问问艾娃
But if you need some cash, I could, I could ask Ava.
操你妈
Oh, fuck you!
也去你妈的 小婊子
And fuck you, bitchtv
都他妈烂人
Fuckin' motherfuckers!
-肏 -我的天
Fuck! Ava: Jesus Christ.
都是烂人
Kathleen: Motherfucker!
我的天
Oh God.
迈克 我说了多少次了
Ava: Michael, I keep asking you
你得带着药
to keep your pills on you.
要是我不在这儿怎么办
What if I'm not here?
-艾娃 -你的心脏
Ava- - - Your heart.
只是一见到凯瑟琳
It's just seeing Kathleen
我的血压就飙升
makes my blood pressure spike.
我去找 让马克给我按摩一下
I'll get a massage from Jean Marc.
亲爱的
Darling
或许你应该重新考虑下
Perhaps you should reconsider.
我有点担心
I worry.
我的钱 我的事业
You know, my money, my career,
还有这一切
all of...this.
你想念镁光灯了
You miss the limelight.
但我不想和凯瑟琳一起
But with Kathleen?
拜托
Oh, come on.
那都是30年前的事了
It was 30 years ago.
你们肯定都成熟了不少
I'm sure you've both grown since then.
你这个爱操纵人 撒谎成性的泼妇
You manipulating, lying shrew!
成熟点吧 你现在是小白脸了
Oh, grow up, you re a kept man.
早该习惯接受女人的指令了
You should be used to taking direction from a woman.
我是绝对不可能
There is no way
让你来指导这出戏的
I'm letting you direct this damn play!
那真是不好意思了 我就是导演
Whoops, I am.
如果你看过合同
And you would have known that
或者让别人给你读过合同
had you read your contract
你就会清楚这一点
or had someone read it to you.
好极了 我这是在地狱里吧
Oh, okay, great. I'm in hell!
赶紧把这条狗给我弄走
And get this dog off the stage
不然它就要被我当球踢了
before I kick it for three points.
过来 福斯
Come here, Fosse.
请问可以先讨论一下
Woman: Um, could we possibly discuss
我这个角色的畸形足问题吗
my character's clubfoot for just a moment?
如果能有真正畸形足的人来指导
Because I would feel personally a lot more comfortable
我个人觉得公
if somebody from the clubfoot community
更好一点
were advising.
-我的天 认真的吗 -是啊
Oh God. Really? Rebecca: Yeah.
你只要瘸着走就可以了 亲爱的
Kathleen: Just get out there and hobble, honey.
这是午餐菜单先生
That's the lunch menu, sir.
给我来个总会三明治 再来把枪
I'll have a club sandwich with a side order of a gun.
还有 哈里 希望不会太麻烦你
Um, uh, and also, Harry, if it's not too much trouble,
谢谢 我想要一杯木槿茶好吗
thanks, could you get me a hibiscus tea, please?
加奶 但不要杏仁奶
With milk. Um, but not almond milk.
我知道大家都爱喝 但我对
I know people like it, but I'm allergic
所有坚果和豆类都过敏
to all tree nuts and legumes, actually.
-我想也是 -我真的是
Of course, you are. Well, no, I am.
所以如果那些狗零食是用花生做的
So if those dog treats are peanut- based,
因为那闻起来很像是花生做的
because they smell peanut- based
上面也写着花生酱
and they say peanut butter on them,
我就真的可能出现过敏性休克
I could go into anaphylactic shock actually.
等下 那他妈是什么
Hold on. What the fuck is that?
什么
What?
你大腿上那个
That thing on your lap.
那是什么
What is it?
我的剧本吗
My script?
你需要一个会脱稿的人
Would you like a representative
来指导一下你吗
of the off- book community present?
这不是你玩的抖音 小鬼
You know, this is not a TikTok, baby.
这是我的舞台
This is my stagel
你背不出台词还演什么戏啊
And you show up knowing your goddamn lines.
该死的年轻人
These fucking millennials.
不用担心 你做得很好了
Don't worry. You re doing great.
你坚持的时间已经超过约翰·斯塔莫斯了
You've already lasted longer than John Stamos.
我的舞台监督比尔呢
Where is my stage manager Bill?
-是菲尔 -好 比尔
Phil. Kathleen: Okay, Bill,
我们要按照1991年的样子
we are going to run this play
完全复刻这台戏
the exact same way we did in 1991.
最后一幕
The timing on my trapdoor exit
我从活板门离开的时机
at the finale
必须完全一致
must be exactly the same.
我们现在不用活板门下人了
Well, we don't do trapdoor drops anymore.
这不安全
It, it isn't safe.
掉下去就是15英尺深
There's a 15- foot drop down
直接到混凝土地面上 按照会规
to a concrete floor underneath, and union regulations state- -
我有一年每天晚上都那么摔
Okay, I did that drop every night for one year.
用弗兰克·里奇的话说 这就是有效的
Frank Rich called it"effective"
那是很久
Okay, well, that was a long time, uh, uh
你说啊 以前
Say the word"ago. "
说啊
Kathleen: Go ahead.
我要你说出来
: I want you to.
我会尽量做得安全
I'll make it as safe as I can.
这不怪你 菲尔
Don't knock yourself out, Phil.
好了 所有人 快点
Kathleen: Okay, everyone, come on.
我们有四天时间来实现奇迹
We have four days to make magic happen here.
各就各位
Places, everybody.
就位
Places.
好了 各位 复习一下
Kathleen: Okay, people, to review- -
每次有军用飞机飞过
Every time a military jet flies over,
舞台上的东西都得抖起来
I want everything on this stage to shake.
抖起来 明白了吗 全部
Shakel You got it. Everything.
-明白 -在第三遍飞过的时候
Crew Member Yes, ma'am. Now, on the third flyover,
那就是准备要进迈克的独白了
that is the cue for Michael's monologue.
如果他能瞄准的话
If he can manage to hit his mark.
这够大吗 你看得见吗
Is that big enough? Can you see it?
好了 比尔
Okay. Now, Bill
比尔 我要过一遍我的独白
Bill, I would like to run through my monologue
直到最后 直到活板门下落
all the way till the end till the trapdoor fall.
我是菲尔
: It's Phil.
都准备好了 一切就绪
Yeah, we're ready! Everything's good!
彭萨科拉的那年冬天很冷
Kathleen: It was cold in Pensacola that winter.
冷得不自然
Unnatural cold.
来得太早的霜迟迟不肯离去
Frost that comes too soon and stays too long.
可能永远不会离去
Maybe forever.
雾气升起
The mist rises up and...
别动
Don't move!
雾气升起 遮盖住你的脚面
The mist rises up and covers your toes.
然后到腰
Then your waist.
那波浪
The waves
想要延伸到云端
They want to meet the clouds.
母亲和孩子伸出手
The mother and child reaching out.
寻找彼此
...for each other...
操你妈的
Oh, goddamn you!
-搞什么啊 -凯瑟琳
What the hell...- Hey, Kathleen.
你过去之后能不能帮我
Why don't you grab me some extra thousand island dressing
多拿点千岛酱过来
while you're back there.
-我靠 -垫子到位了
Son of a bitch! - Mats work.
-喂 -搞什么
Hey. Kathleen: What?
我差点摔断脖子
I almost broke my goddamn neck!
-我受够了 我不干了 -很好
I'm done. I'm out. I quit. - Good.
你现在走 就要付给我
You walk out now, you're on the hook
20万违约金
for a $200, 000 kill fee.
所以不如你先找你老婆聊聊
So maybe you want to talk to your wife about it first.
毕竟是她给你发零花钱
The one who pays your allowance.
20万也值了
It's worth every penny!
我倒是没有这么肯定
Kathleen: You know, I'm not so sure,
因为如果她知道
because I think if she knew
你的那些风流事了 可能就不会给你钱了
about all your dalliances, maybe not so much.
行啊 你想跟我同归于尽是吧
Alright. You want some mutually- assured destruction?
-是啊 -没问题
- Yeah. - I got you, baby.
-放马过来吧 -因为我正在写回忆录
Bring it. - Because I m working on my memoirs,
我有一整章来写
and I got a whole chapter about
阿卡普尔科
: ...Acapulco.
你签了保密协议的
You signed an NDA.
现在我无所畏惧了
Yeah, well, now I got NFs to G.
懂吗 我会陪你演完这场戏
Alright, I'll do your damn play,
但我告诉你 你的末日就要来了
but I tell you this- the doomsday clock is ticking.
今晚幕布落下的时候
And when the curtains drop on this play tonight,
你就可以和演员生涯告别了
you can kiss your career goodbye.
建议你看看你的婚前协议
You might want to check your prenup.
因为明天
Because tomorrow,
艾娃会收到一封邮件
Ava is getting a little info in the mail
有关那个柴娜的
about Chyna with a"Y. "
我不开玩笑
I'm not bluffing.
我知道
I know.
你演技不够好
You're not a good enough actor.
好了 还有5分钟开演 各位 5分钟
Okay Five minutes to call, people. Five minutes.
-找到了 -谢谢你
- Found it. - Thank you.
我给你弄了个前排座位
Michael: I got you a seat right up front
这样我能看到你
so I can see you.
我真幸运
Lucky me.
祝你好运
Break a leg.
艾娃 亲爱的
Ava. Ava darling.
我想谢谢你
I just wanted to thank you.
什么
Sorry?
我知道是你说服迈克
Well, I know that you convinced Michael
和我一起演戏的 所以
to do the play with me, and.
真的 谢谢
I just...thank you.
凯瑟琳
Oh, Kathleen. Oh.
我知道跟你合作的噩梦程度
No, see, I knew that working with you would be
绝对能彻底消灭
such a fucking nightmare that it would kill off
迈克演戏的念头
Michael's silly little acting bug
一劳永逸 这不就成了
once and for all, and voila.
所以 谢谢你才对
So, thank you. -
疯子
Psycho.
那婊子的牙都不齐
That bitch's teeth don't even match.
这他妈搞什么呢
The fuck is going on here?
祝你好运 迈克
Break a leg, Michael.
最好别让凯瑟琳看到你拿着这些
Better not let Kathleen catch you with those.
她能怎么 炒我鱿鱼吗
What is she going to do, fire me?
那我求之不得
A man can dream.
雄猫战斗机吗
Tomcat?
不 那是幻影
No, that's a Phantom.
真不知道他们何必费这么犬力气
Don't know why they bother.
他们说士兵们圣诞节前就能回家了
They say our boys will be home by Christmas.
你怕什么
Michael: What are you afraid of?
她会变成什么样
Kathleen: What will become of her?
我怕她内心
I'm afraid that, that she has
有太多我们的影子
too much of both of us inside her.
我怕她铁石心肠
I'm afraid that she has a gunmetal heart.
就像你一样
Like you.
夏天 感觉就像冬天
Summer felt like winter
感觉就像春天
felt like spring.
该死的骗子
Fucking hack!
这男人太可悲了
Pathetic excuse for a man.
你个臭女人
You ball- busting harpy.
去他妈的烂货
Goddamn son of a fucking piece of shit.
老掉牙的过气女星
Michael: You washed- up has- been.
你这可悲的挑剔混蛋
Kathleen: You pathetic preening prick!
你太失败了
You are such a failure.
你觉得你是个女演员吗
You think you're an actress?
你就是个笑话
You're a joke.
你就是个活生生的失败作品
A lying, philandering failure.
整个剧组以前都在笑你
The whole crew used to laugh at you.
还女演员呢 就一破烂货
Actress? More like hacktress.
你个无能的傻子
Kathleen: You impotent baby.
我到底是怎么忍你这么多年的
How the fuck did I put up with you all these years?
你这皱巴巴的老太婆
Michael: You shriveled prune. Ah, ah!
不如你的鸡巴那么皱巴巴
Kathleen: Not as shriveled as your tiny little dick!
混蛋
Asshole.
你这狂妄 背后捅刀的贱人
You vain, backstabbing hag.
这是什么样的上帝
What kind of god!
鲍比
Bobby.
鲍比 我希望我的心能够翱翔
Bobby, I want my heart to soar.
我要在你坟头跳舞
I will dance on your grave.
我要在你坟头撒尿
I'll piss on your grave.
感觉风暴快要来子
Kathleen: It feels like a storm is brewin'.
你关窗了吗 亲爱的
Did you close the windows, sweetheart?
宝贝 我今天在超市看到克劳福德家的小伙子了
Oh baby. I saw the Crawford boy down the supermarket today.
他现在在基地工作了
He works at the base now.
-别说了 妈 -别说什么
Rebecca: Stop it, Mama. - Kathleen: Stop what?
别说了 别以为
Stop it! Just stop thinking
还会有男人要我
that any man would ever want me.
不 我不是说你的脚
Oh, no, I didn't say that about your foot.
-不 -不
Rebecca: No! Kathleen: Oh no.
人总说彭萨科拉有两种人
They say that there are two types of men in Pensacola:
飞行员 和让他们能上天的人
pilots, and the men who keep'em up in the air.
如果你忘了 他们会提醒你
And if you forget, they'll remind you.
有些人说这就是为什么飞机飞得那么低
Some folks say that that's why they fly their jets so low.
让我们打翻早晨的咖啡
Make us spill our morning coffee.
永远带着恐惧
Always looking up at the skies
仰望天空
in fear.
为了保证我们在自己的位置上
Just to keep us in our place.
小心
Woman: Look out! -
迈克
Michael!
艾娃
Ava.
艾娃 艾娃
Ava! Ava!
我的天
Man: Oh, my God! -
不
Oh no!
我们这里应该都完事儿了
Officer: I think we've got everything we need.
再次深表哀悼
And again, Tm so sorry for your loss.
谢谢你
Thank you.
你们单独聊聊吧
Oh, I'll give you guys some privacy.
我只是想说 《幽灵与警察》
I just want you to know that "Spooky and the Cop"
是我选择成为执法人员的理由
made me choose a career in law enforcement.
谢谢你 这话我真的听了太多次了
Thank you. I can't tell you how many times I've heard that.
那是这辈子的最佳演出
That was the performance of a lifetime.
你做到了 亲爱的
You did it, darling.
我们做到了
We did it.
拜托 你往顾客身上扔小费了
Come on, you threw a tip at a customer.
那就一毛而已
You know what, it was a dime.
你还吃了别人的培根
And you ate someone's bacon.
他们无视我
They were ignoring me.
你是我招到过的最差的服务生
You are the worst waitress I've ever had.
我可是绿色地带开过老乡村店的
And I ran a Cracker Barrel in the Green Zone.
最后一句完全没必要
That last part was unnecessary.
但还是谢谢你的付出
But thank you for your service.
行吧 天啊
Okay. God.
虽然是被解雇了吧
Well, as firings go,
但我也确实干得不怎么样
hardly my best work.
对日场的人来说还不错
Not bad for a matinee
你知道还有哪里
You happen to know anyplace else
招低水平服务生的吗
that's looking for a subpar waitress
不要简历和推荐信的那种
that doesn't require paperwork or references?
还真有 工作时间减半 小费不错
Well, actually, half hours, good tips.
没有福利
Mm, no benefits.
看时节的活 付的现金
Seasonal work, so it pays cash.
如果你有兴趣 我可以帮你说几句好话
I can put in a good word for you if you're interested.
听着还挺完美的
Well, that actually sounds pretty perfect.
干什么活
What's the catch?
-费城 -在
*Philadelphia**Yeah*
-我有帮到你们吗 -有
* Am I helping ya? k * (eah*
你们的好爸爸是谁 我是说
*Who's your daddy? And by that, I mean*
-开国之父 -富兰克林
*Founding Father? *Franklin*
-谁 本·富兰克林吗 -是你
* Who? Ben Franklin**You*
毫不意外
*It's no surprise *
我健康 有钱 聪明
*I'm healthy and wealthy and wise*
我被雷劈过
*I've been struck by lightning*
任何人都看得出来
*Anyone can see*
大型暴风雨加上一只老风筝
*A great big storm and a little old kite*
帮我找到了关键
*Helped me find the key*
这是地狱吧
This is hell.
我只爱本杰明
*I'm all about the Benjamin*
本杰明·富兰克林
* Benjamin Franklin...*
好了 各位 复习一下
Kathleen: Okay, people, to review- -
每次有军用飞机飞过
Every time a military jet flies over,
舞台上的东西都得抖起来
I want everything on this stage to shake.
早 杰尔 想我了吗
Morning, Jer. Miss me?
嘘 我在听技市人员彩排
Shh! I'm listening to the tech rehearsal.
我就当是想我了 这是什么
I'll take that as a yes. What is this.
比尔 比尔
Kathleen: Bill! Bill!
他们这周在排的大戏是什么
...the big magilla they've been working on all week.
那是凯瑟琳·汤森和迈克·格雷夫斯
That s Kathleen Townsend and Michael Graves
在演《彭萨科拉的幽灵》
doing"Ghosts of Pensacola" here.
我都快疯了
I'm losing my shit.
别别别 那不是吃的
Hey, hey. No, that's not food.
那是道具 道具食物
It's a prop. Prop food.
-尊重一点 -这是食物
Respect it. Well, this is, this is food.
这是食物 你疯了
This is food. You're nuts.
听好了 所有食物都不能放花生
Listen up. No peanuts in anything.
另一个演员有过敏
The third banana onstage has an allergy.
这是今晚限定的宴会活动
It's our one- night only gala event.
是满座的 而且不是每天都能进到比目鱼
It's a sellout, and I don't get halibut every day.
-所以所有人都得给我绷紧了 -行
: So I need everyone on their toes. Okay.
等等 查莉 别
Man: Wait. Charlie. No!
操你妈的
Kathleen: Oh, goddamn you!
搞什么啊
What the hell? l
凯瑟琳
Michael: Hey, Kathleen.
你过去之后能不能帮我
Why don't you grab me some extra
多拿点千岛酱过来
thousand island dressing while you're back there?
怎么了
What?
我靠
Michael: Son of a bitch!
垫子到位了
Phil: Mats work!
把那个无知的人给我带过来
Bring me the Philistine.
天 别 别再弄坏假发了
Oh, please, God, no, don't break another wig.
-喂 -你给我听好了
Hey. Now you listen to me.
演员表演的时候
When an actor is performing,
你不能打喷嚏 不能呼吸
you don't sneeze, you don't breathe.
你他妈不能把冰
You don't dump fucking ice
倒进冰沙机里去
in a fucking froze dispenser.
好吧 听着 小姐 我真的 我只是
Okay, listen, lady, I, I, I, I really. I just
我只是在完成自己的工作
I'mjust doing my job here.
怎么 你以为大家是来这儿吃饭的吗
What, do you think people come here for the food?
是 算是吧
Well, yeah. I mean, kind of.
我只是个服务生
Uh...You know, I'm just a waitress.
这地方吃饭还得听戏
It's not really my fault that this place came
又不是我的错
with a talking wall.
那个舞台是个神坛
That stage is an altar
我们在追寻真相的过程中
where we bare our souls
袒露灵魂
in search of the truth.
你需要尊重这一点 小姑娘
Now you will respect that, young lady,
不如你自已撞墙去吧
or you can hit the fucking bricks.
也对
The truth.
是 抱歉
Wow. Uh, yeah, sorry.
我只是 碰巧比较了解真相
I just, I happen to know a thing or two about the truth,
所以我这么说吧
so I'll tell you.
帕特里克·斯威兹《威龙杀阵》
You got Patrick Swayze, "Roadhouse. "
詹妮弗·杰森·李《双面女郎》
Jennifer Jason Leigh, Single White Female. "
克里斯蒂安·史莱特《真实罗曼史》
Christian Slater, "True Romance. "
这都是真的 而你
Truth, truth, truth. Now, you.
我碰巧在你大吼的时候
Uh, well, I did happen to catch
听到了几个词
a few words through the rainstorm.
我跟你说实话我一个字都不信你
And I'll tell you the truth, I didn't believe a single word.
甚至可以说 这是我这辈子
In fact, I would say that that's maybe the biggest batch
我这一辈子里听到过的
of bullshit I've heard in my whole,
最大的谎话
yeah, whole entire life.
老天
Jesus.
我明白了 我自己滚出去
I get it. I'll see myself out.
已经有30年没人这么跟我说话了
I haven't been spoken to that way in 30 years.
-所以我没被炒鱿鱼吗 -炒鱿鱼
Does this mean I'm not fired. Kathleen: Fired?
天 你这是在给我黄金
My God. What you're giving me is gold.
这是燃料
It's fuel.
我就靠这个活着 我会利用它
I live off it. I use it.
你摘掉了耳塞是你走运
And you're lucky you took those earbuds out
因为你马上要听到这辈子的最佳演出了
because you're about to hear the performance of a lifetime.
我喜欢你的作品
I love your work.
你在凯瑟琳·汤森的
You survived a face full
当面臭骂之后活下来了 小姑娘
of Kathleen Townsend, kid.
感觉你挺正常的 菲尔
Uh, I mean, you seem like a normal guy, Phil.
你怎么忍受这些剧院人的
How are you putting up with these theater people?
你得爱他们 得理解他们
Well, you got to love em, and you got to understand'em.
凯瑟琳说的 也没说错
I mean, what Kathleen said, she's right.
舞台上的演出就类似魔法
What happens on that stage is a kind of magic.
我能见证那些人第一次
And I get to see someone hit with it,
被那些戏所触动 所改变的样子
truly transformed by it for the first time every show.
所以我才坚持在做这一行
That's probably why I keep doing it.
那你人比我好 菲尔
Well, you're a better man than me, Phil.
我都是真心话 不过
Well, everything I said and, but also,
杰克·丹尼威士忌
Jack Daniels
是我的戏剧顾问
is my dramaturg.
这才是能支撑我继续工作的加油鼓劲
Now you see, this is the kind of pep talk I can get behind.
就一晚上 小姑娘
One night only, kid.
等首演完 这就都结束了
After opening, this is all over.
敬首演
To opening night.
不好意思 亲爱的
Ava : Excuse me, darling.
你能不能把我灌醉
Can you get me absolutely shit- faced?
我会保证你永远有酒喝的
Oh, you'll never see the bottom of that glass.
你是说像你一样吗
Michael: You mean like you?
夏天 感觉就像冬天
Summer felt like winter
感觉就像春天
felt like spring
我甚至想念嘻哈本·富兰克林了
Makes you miss the hip- hop Ben Franklin.
我不知道那些季节是什么样的感觉
I didn't know what the seasons felt like- -
老掉牙的过气女星
Michael: ...you washed- up has- been.
你这可悲的挑剔混蛋
Kathleen: You pathetic, preening prick!
你们听得开心就好
Glad someone's riveted.
你觉得你是个女演员吗 你就是个笑话
Michael: ...actress. You're a joke.
凯瑟琳和迈克在后台吵架
Kathleen and Michael are fighting backstage,
他们忘记关麦了
and they forgot to turn off their mics.
失败作品
Kathleen: ...failure.
整个剧组以前都在笑你
Michael: The whole crew used to laugh at you.
-真是不开玩笑 -还女演员呢 就一破烂货
- You weren't kidding. - Michael: Actress? More like hacktress.
等下 要是这我们能听到
Hold on, if we can hear this,
你知道还有谁能听到吗
you realize who else can hear it, right?
我总是问 自己为什么 上帝 为什么
Rebecca: And I always ask myself, why, God, why?
-但鲍比总是能让我觉得 -老太婆
- But Bobby always made me feel Michael: Prune!
不如你的鸡巴那么皱巴巴
Kathleen: Not as shriveled as your tiny little dick!
混蛋
Asshole!
你这狂妄 背后捅刀的贱人
Michael: You vain, backstabbing hag.
谁在说话啊 是幽灵吗
Who's talking? Is that the ghost?
这是我唯一的愿望
That's all I've ever wanted.
感觉风暴快要来了
Oh. Feels like a storm is brewin'.
我今天在超市看到克劳福德家的小伙子了
I saw the Crawford boy down the supermarket today.
他问起你了
He asked about you.
-谢了 -别说了 妈
Thanks. - Rebecca: Oh, stop it, Mama!
别以为还会有男人要我
Stop thinking that any man would ever want me.
杀了我吧
Kill me.
人总说彭萨科拉有两种人
Michael: There are two kinds of men in Pensacola- -
飞行员 和让他们能上天的人
pilots, and the men who keep 'em up in the air.
如果你忘了 他们会提醒你
And if you forget, they'll remind you.
你看凯瑟琳
Watch Kathleen.
有些人说这就是为什么
Michael: Some folks say that's why-
她好入戏
She's so present.
看看她
Look at her.
她眼里的恐惧和期待
Fear and anticipation in her eyes.
你说的对
Yeah, you're right.
这是我第一次真的信她
This is the first time I've really believed her.
小\l
Look out!
艾娃
Michael: Ava!
迈克
Ava: Michael!
艾娃
Michael: Ava!
艾娃 艾娃
Michael: Ava! Ava!
我的天
Audience Member Oh, my God!
听着 这不是你的错
Charlie: I mean, look, it's not your fault.
有个女人在我的舞台上摔死了
A woman fell to her death on my stage.
这怎么不是我的错了
How is it not my fault?
因为那只是个意外 好吗
Because it was a crazy acciclent, okay?
你想想 有多少地方
I mean, just think about all the things
出问题了
that had to go wrong.
大灯掉下来了 迈克心脏病发
The light fell. Michael had a heart attack.
他老婆在喝了我给她倒的好东西之后
His wife ran up with his pills
带着他的药冲上舞台
after I poured her a bottle of the good stuff, by the way.
要是这些事里缺了任何一环
If any one of those things hadn't happened,
我们现在就已经在垃圾桶旁边
you and me will be outside by the dumpsters
给克里斯托弗·诺兰的电影打分排名了
ranking Christopher Nolan movies right now.
不 只要幕布拉开
No, as soon as the curtain goes up
那就都是我的责任
it's all my responsibility.
看来我是走运
I guess I'm lucky.
警察只要查查我的保温杯
All the cops had to do is check my thermos,
我就要去坐牢了
and I'd be sitting in a cell.
拜托 我了解你
Come on. I know you.
你只是需要一些爱尔兰咖啡鸡尾酒
It was just a little Irish coffee
来放松 对吧
to take the edge off, right?
是 我也是这样以为的
Yeah, that's what I thought.
可能是我酒量不行了
Maybe I'm a lightweight now.
我肯定是检查过活栓和垫子的
I know I checked that bolt and those pads.
这是我记忆里最后一件事在我
It's the last thing I remember before...
我的天
Oh God.
Oh, my God.
我的天
老天 你这是能随便放的吗
Jesus. Should you be leaving those out?
宝贝 我是个女演员
Baby, I'm an actress.
要是我的化妆间没有安必恩
If I didn't have a bottle of Ambien in my dressing room,
别人才会好奇呢
people would ask questions.
是啊 我们真是对不起菲尔
Yeah, it's too bad about Phil.
他又不是坐牢了
It's not like he's in jail or anything.
他只是出了点小问题而已
He just went a little overboard.
你是真想念当年自己扮演祸水红颜的时候啊
Wow. You really missed your window for playing a femme fatale.
我可以让全世界回想起来
Now, I can remind the whole world
凯瑟琳·汤森有多厉害
what Kathleen Townsend can do.
全世界都在看
And the world is watching.
你在说什么
What are you talking about?
我们上热搜了 宝贝
We are trending, baby.
现在
Right now,
所有人都在看着我们
people are watching us.
他们真的在看
They are really watching.
我刚才没机会表演完我的独白
And I never got to deliver my monologue.
-不 -没错
No. Yes.
最后一次演出 今晚
One last performance. Tonight.
-不 -为了艾娃
- No. For Ava.
No. For Ava.
不行
Fuck that.
说好的我们去海外躲一年
What happened to we hide out overseas for a year
然后再回来承认关系呢
and then reemerge confessing our love.
那是你写的剧本啊 宝贝
You wrote the script, baby.
我知道 是我写的
I know. I wrote it.
-现在我要改剧市了 -不
- And now I'm flipping it. - No.
我要彻底改掉剧本
I'm flipping the script entirely.
没错 是你的悲剧让我们走到了一起
Yes. Your tragedy is what drew us together.
这风险太大了
It's risky.
宝贝
Oh, baby
你不想现在就跟我在一起吗
don't you want to be together right now?
你不觉得我们应该开始花一花那些
Don't you think we should start spending
她之交易的钱呢
some of that She Trade money.
好
Oh yes.
聚光灯是属于我们的 宝贝
The spotlight's ours, baby.
不要错过它的热量
Let's get it while it's hot.
让我弄清楚
So let me get this straight,
有个女人死在了我们面前
a woman dies right in our faces
他们却不给我们找心理咨询
and instead of giving us grief counseling,
反而要我们工作
we have to work.
剧院人就是这么坚强
Theater people are so strong.
我不知道 但这 这说不通啊
I don't know, it just, it, it doesn't make any sense.
那兄弟都心脏病发了
I mean, the dude had a coronary,
还死了老婆
and then his wife died.
哪个医生会同意啊
Like, what doctor signed off on this?
帮埃德治安官找个位子
Find a seat for Sheriff Ed.
他是《幽灵与警察》的狂热粉丝
He's some crazy"Spooky and the Cop"fan.
我们满座了 如果他没有票
It's a sellout. If he doesn't have a ticket...
他要座位你就给
Give the lawman what he wants.
他刚刚处理了全康涅狄格州
He just dealt with the richest woman in Connecticut
最富有的女人被醉鬼舞台监督害死的案子
getting killed by a drunk stagehand.
拜托 扯淡
Oh, come on. Bullshit.
注意你的言行
Thin ice.
赶紧出去把你的工作做好
Get out there and keep your job
你要干什么
What do you want?
不用担心福斯
Oh, don't worry about Fosse.
他今天很乖
He's very well- behaved today.
我之前就觉得很奇怪
So I thought it was weird
迈克怎么会在复习台词
that Michael was going over his dialogue for the show
毕竟他彩排就一句都没错过
since he didn't miss a single line in rehearsal.
所以我就看了他的大衣口袋 真想不到
So I checked in his coat pocket and lo and behold,
这不是《彭萨科拉的幽灵》的台词
this is not dialogue from"Ghosts of Pensacola. "
是你们俩在我独白的时候
This is the fight that the two of you had
吵架的台词
during my monologue.
你们用来掩饰谋杀艾娃的那一架
The fight that you used to cover up Ava's murder.
亲爱的 我和迈克是在
Sweetheart, Michael and I are workshopping
排练一位优秀新作家的戏
a new play by a brilliant new writer,
我们是在后台对台词
and we're running lines backstage.
要是我看到你们俩在后台在一起
That might fly if I had seen
这可能还说得通
the two of you backstage together.
但我没有 你们都不在
But I didn't. You were gone.
我的独白刚好给你们足够时间
And my monologue gave you just enough time
来破坏大灯和活板门
to sabotage the light and the trapdoor
所以就是你们干的
So you did it.
你看太多犯罪纪录片了
You watch too much"Dateline"
不 但我看了很多
Rebecca: No, but I have been watching
《幽灵与警察》
a heck of a lot of"Spooky and the Cop. "
这一出戏正好就是
And this exact thing happens
第6季第11集的《离开舞台之死》
in season six, episode 11, "Exit Stage Death. "
你们两个懒货连台词都没改
You lazy assholes didn't even bother to change the dialogue.
所以 这是我要的价格
So, um...here's my price.
这是我的银行账户信息
And here is my bank info.
所以如果今晚这出戏演完
So if that money is not in my account
钱还没到我账上
by the end of the play tonight,
我就要去报警了
I'm going to the police.
对哦 还有一件事
Oh, and one last thing.
那段独白我演得无可挑剔
I killed that fucking monologue, okay?
所以你别想再抢我风头
So don't you ever upstage me again.
傻逼老头老太
Fucking boomers.
行 所以我们该怎么办
Okay, what are we going to do?
我们得付钱 没得选了
We have to pay. We have no choice.
我来送道具食物的
Just delivering the prop food.
我是这里的
Oh, I belong here.
对 来送道具食物的
Yeah. Okay, sir, prop food.
老天
Jesus.
还有10分钟开幕
Man: Ten minutes to curtain.
10分钟后开幕
Ten minutes to curtain.
菲尔的开演前检查清单
Phil's preshow checklist.
靠 我得去过一遍检查清单
Oh shit. I got to do the checklist.
哇哦
Charlie: Wow.
开演前他勾了活板门这一项的
He ticked off the flappy door checkbox before the show.
-这儿写着呢 -所以呢
It's here. - Harry: So?
如果他拴上了门
If he secured the flappy door,
那就代表是有人又打开了门闩
that means that someone unsecured it.
也就是说那不是菲尔的错
That means it wasn't Phil's fault
更不是什么意外了
and it wasn't an accident.
除了凯瑟琳
Is anyone else besides Kathleen
还有谁要用活板门下台吗
supposed to go through that flappy door?
她的活板门高光诶 你开什么玩笑
Her big trapdoor moment? Are you kidding me?
也就是说目标是凯瑟琳
That means that Kathleen was the target.
我得给菲尔发个短信
I gotta text Phil.
我的天
Oh, my God.
-喂 -我是查莉
Hey. It's Charlie.
那不是你的错
It wasn't your fault.
是有人故意破坏 破 毁
It was sabotage. S- A- B- O- O...
-好像不太对 -演出马上就要开始了
That doesn't seem right. - The show is about to start
我的天 兄弟 我们刚想清楚
Oh, my God, dude, dude, we just figured out
有人想杀凯瑟琳
that someone is trying to kill Kathleen.
你现在要再给他们一次动手机会吗
Now you're going to give them another whack at the pinata.
但演出马上就要开始了
But the show is about to start!
这不是我的刀子嘴批评家吗
Oh, if it isn't my fiercest critic.
你是准备在我上台之前给我点建议吗
Are you here to give me some notes before my swan song?
那不是菲尔的错
Charlie: It wasn't Phil's fault.
他被人陷害了
He was framed.
我觉得是有人给他下了药
So I think someone drugged him
在活板门上动了手脚
and futzed with the floor door.
我不知道为什么
I mean, I don't know why,
但我觉得凶手的目标是你
but I think you were the target.
会站上活板门的只有你 所以
You're the only one who was supposed to stand on it, so...
我在那上面走了好多次
I walk across it many times
都没掉下去
and did not fall through.
那应该是够结实的
My blocking is very vigorous.
-好吧 -听着
Okay, uh - Look,
剧院里是经常出事的
things happen in the theater all the time.
整个布景都可能垮掉
Entire sets collapse.
通电的线就这么露在外面
Live wires get exposed,
电倒演员
they electrocute actors.
但我们依然在坚持
But we persevere.
抱歉 我觉得你没听懂我的意思
Hey, I- I'm so sorry. I don't think you're hearing me.
这是有人想杀你
Someone's trying to kill you.
我不会再让你出去的
I'm not going to let you go back out there.
我的麦已经开了
I'm already on.
赶紧出去吧
Now get out of my room.
服装师
Wardrobe.
雄猫战斗机吗
Tomcat?
不 那是幻影
No, that's a Phantom.
真不知道他们何必费这么大力气
I don't know why they bother.
他们说士兵们圣诞节前就能回家了
They say our boys will be home by Christmas.
叫38
: Cue 38.
听着 那是菲尔吗
: Listen, is that Phil?
给我
Give me that.
-菲尔 菲尔 -嗨
- Phil, Phil. - Phil: Hey.
听着 我不明白
Listen, I, I, I don't get it.
那个栓在艾娃走上去之前
I mean, the bolt must have been in place
一定是在那里的
until Ava walked across it.
你还见过有谁在舞台下面吗
Did you see anybody else down there?
没有
Phil: Nobody.
听着 查莉 我很感谢
Look, Charlie, I appreciate
你想帮 我但你别管了
what you're trying to do, but just let it go.
我不能不管 菲尔
Charlie: No can do, Phil.
我就跟《盗火线》最后的德尼罗一样
I'm like De Niro at the end of"Heat, "man.
所以别放弃
So stay tuned.
我需要看一下昨晚演出的视频
I need to see the video of last night's show.
你请便 接过这个诅咒
Well, be my guest. Take the curse off me.
这就跟《午夜凶铃》里的录像带一样
It's like the video from"The Ring, "
但现在菲尔不在了 轮到我当舞台监督了
but with Phil gone, I'm the stage manager
我能参考的只有这段视频
and I have nothing to go on except this video
和菲尔昨晚的笔记
and Phil's notes from last night.
等等等等
Charlie: Hey, hey, hey.
那是什么
What is that?
那是演吗
Is that smoke?
看上去像是干冰
Harry: Looks like dry ice.
你们把干冰都放哪儿
Where do you keep this, uh, dry ice?
你没事吧
Man: You okay?
天 我得去找凯瑟林
Jesus. I- I got to talk to Kathleen.
等等 别
Hey, wait. Stop!
你看到这个没有 这是舞台界限
See that? It's a sight line.
你不能过去 过去就上台了
You can't cross it, you're in the play.
鲍比是我未曾想到的礼物
Kathleen: Bobby was my unexpected gift.
虽然很可耻
Shameful as it was,
但我依然爱他
I loved him so.
他爱那些流星
He liked the stars that moved fast,
就像他的飞机一样
like his aircraft.
我弄清楚了
Charlie: Hey, I figured it out.
栓子是干冰
The bolt was dry ice.
让我说完 也就是说肯定有人
Excuse me. That means that someone definitely- -
蟋蟀真是活跃
The crickets are certainly very active.
快下来 下台
...off! Off the stage.
这些蟋蟀真是疯了
Oh, these crickets are wild.
下台
Off the stage.
这些蟋蟀得闭嘴
They need to stop, the crickets.
下台
Charlie: Get off the stage.
你得闭嘴
You need to stop now.
你得下台
You need to get off the stage.
-贾瑞特 -老天
Um, GarrettJesus!
你怎么在屋里抽那脏东西
...what are you doing smoking that filthy thing in the house.
要是不小心 黛西会得胸膜炎的
You'll give Daisy pleurisy if you don't watch out.
妈 我也抽烟的
Mother, I smoke.
你很惊讶吗
Does that shock you?
没错 我会抽烟
That's right. I smoke cigarettes.
你的女儿 你的小女儿
Your daughter, your little girl.
-谢天谢地 -它很适合我 能让我的灵魂安稳下来
- Thank God. Rebecca: It suits me. It calms my spirit
-嗨 -让我的大脑放松
- Hey! ...and it eases my mind.
好吧 看来她
Uh, yeah, well, looks like we got us
真是个烟民 萨凡纳
a real smoker, Savannah.
挺好的 黛西
Good for you, Daisy.
你干什么呢
Hey, what are you doing?
我自己就很享受
I myself enjoy smoking
在窗边抽烟
by the window over here.
放开我 放开我
Let me go. Let me go!
我们都会死于烟
Smoke is going to be the death of all of us.
我知道了
I know what let's do
我们一起烤点什么吧
let's bake something together
佛岛酸橙派吧
A key lime pie.
就像你小时候一样
Like when you were a little girl.
我已经不是小姑娘了妈妈
I'm not a little girl anymore, Mama.
是迈克
Charlie: It was Michael!
他手上有冻伤 因为他用干冰
His fingers are burned from the dry ice
做了手脚
he used to rig the floor.
这里面应该是有牛奶的
There's supposed to be milk in here somewhere.
在这儿呢
Oh, there.
迈克全程一直都在舞台上
Michael was on stage the entire time.
不 畸形足小姐的独白 有整整三分钟呢
No, the chubby foot monologue, that was three minutes.
-他可以 -我们吵架的时候
He could have- - Our argument.
大家都听到了 你也听到了
Everyone heard it. You heard it.
你他妈到底在说什么
Now, what the fuck are you even talking about?
你差点就要死了 女士
You almost caught the bus, lady.
那个掉下来的大灯救了你一命
That falling light saved your life.
如果我是冰箱 你会关注我吗
...if I were a refrigerator, would you pay attention to me?
没错 你觉得他对灯动手脚是为了自杀吗
Exactly. And do you think he rigged the light to kill himself?
大灯
The light?
像他老爹一样
Michael: ...watching life like his old man!
我为什么要逼鲍比 为什么
Why did I push Bobby? Why?
你只让他要志向高远
You only told him to aim high.
我们对孩子不都是这么期望的吗
Isn't that what we all want for our children?
但当我看到他穿着那身蓝色制服的时候
But when I saw him in those dress blues.
他天生就是要飞翔的
Kathleen: Oh, that boy was born to fly.
我们的儿子 他快乐吗
Was he happy, our son?
他快乐吗
Was he happy?
宝贝 你我都清楚
Kathleen: Oh, baby, you and I both know that
鲍比最开心的时候
Bobby was never happy
就是在天上与鸟儿肩并肩的时候
other than when he was up there flying with the birds.
如果这有意义的话 如果有任何意义的话
If that matters. If anything matters.
我爱你
I love you.
这就是最重要的
That matters.
这是真话
The truth.
我也爱你
I love you, too.
嗨 嗨 畸形足小姐
Hey, hey, chubby foot.
我们碰到了点问题
Uh, we've got a situation here.
你是谁啊 你是刚从灯架上下来吗
Who are you? Did you just come down from the lights?
这不重要 我之前以为
It doesn't matter. So I thought
迈克是想杀凯瑟琳
that Michael was trying to kill Kathleen,
但我弄错了
but I was wrong.
他是想杀他老婆 他们是一伙的
It was his wife, and they were in it together.
迈克和凯瑟琳
Michael and Kathleen.
他们不是互相仇恨的
You see, they don't hate each other.
-他们是相爱的 -你跟我说这个干什么
They love each other. - Why are you telling me this?
-我要上台了 -因为
- I'm about to go on. Oh, because...
不好意思 你可以证明这件事
Excuse me. You can prove it.
那是在你在台上独白的时候
You see, it was during your foot club speech thing.
他在对活板门动手脚
He was futzing with the flappy door,
而她在乱搞大灯
and she, she was messing with the light.
你那有多长 3分钟是吧
What was it? Three minutes, right?
对 但我看到他们俩一起在后台了
Yes. But I saw the two of them backstage together,
所以那不可能是他们干的 好吗
so they couldn't possibly have done it, okay.
你能别烦我了吗 我要上台了
So...will you leave me alone. I have to go on.
等等 你为什么要说谎
Wait, why are you lying?
难道你也爱他吗
Wait, are you in love with him too?
你能不能别烦我
Will you please leave me alone?
你们是三人行吗
Are you a thruple?
-靠 -妈妈
Shit. Rebecca: Mama.
你觉得比利·克劳福德会来电话吗
Do you think Billy Crawford will come calling?
我可以打电话问问他妈妈吧
Oh, I could call his mother and ask her, couldn't I?
算了 妈妈 当我没提
No, never mind, Mama. Forget I mentioned it.
我会的
Kathleen: I will.
你觉得会不会有什么迹象
Do you think there could be a sign or somethin'?
这群演员 我靠
Fucking actors, man.
畸形足 够硬核
Chubby foot. Very hardcore.
闭嘴 闭嘴
Quiet, quiet, heyl
谁想来点好吃的
Who wants a yummy, yummy
花生酱小零食呢
little peanut butter treat?
我靠
1a1 ie Oh shit.
靠靠靠
Shit, shit, shit.
看 亲爱的 我给你做了点小零食
Kathleen: Look, honey, I made you a little snack.
老天
Charlie: Oh, Jesus.
-谢了 妈妈 -靠
Thank you, Mama. Charlie: Oh shit.
道具是谁吃的
Who eats the prop?
-混合饼干是谁吃的 -瑞贝卡
Which actor eats the Chex Mix? - Rebecca.
不 他们往里面放了花生酱 他们又要杀人了
No, they put peanut butter in it. They're gonna kill again.
靠
Shit.
我当时还好年轻
Michael: I was so young.
弗罗里达州立大学在找后卫
Florida State was looking for a fullback.
教练看上了我
Coach was scouting me,
你觉得我想18岁就结婚吗
You think I wanted to get married at 18?
你觉得我想吗
Kathleen: Do you think I did?
我 我是彭萨科拉的幽灵
I am, I am a ghost of Pensacola.
你不是来吃东西的
Uh, and you are not here to eat.
你要和大家聊聊你的畸形足
You are here to talk about your chubby foot
还有你的感受
and, uh, feelings.
不要让你母亲
Do not let your mother
毒害了你的灵魂
poison your spirit
不要让她逼疯你
and drive you nuts.
现在 我要回到
And now I will return
彭萨科拉的灵界
to the spirit realm of Pensacola.
Okay. 好
拜拜
: Goodbye!
搞什么 你看我干什么
What, why are you looking at me?
-我做了什么 -我说什么了吗 -听着 瑞贝卡
What'd I do? What'd I say? - Listen, Rebec- -
黛西 听着 黛西
I mean, Daisy. Listen, Daisy.
你妈这跟我都没关系
I had nothing to do with your mom- -
-妈 -怎么了
Mama. Kathleen: What?
爸 你们已经失去了一个孩子
Daddy. You already lost one child,
差点失去另一个
and you almost lost another one.
所以现在 我的爱的代价
So now, the price of my love
翻倍了
has doubled,
我要求立刻看到它
and I demand to see it immediately.
开什么玩笑 就现在
Are you fucking kidding me? Immediately!
夏天 感觉就像冬天
Summer felt like winter.
你怎么能不跟我说 就这么动手了呢
How could you do that without talking to me first?
什么 哦对
What? Oh, yes.
你想什么呢
What were you thinking?
总得有人动手
Someone had to do it.
你疯了
Michael: You're insane.
我们可以付钱给她的 这样都结束了
We could have paid her off. This would all be over.
你别太天真了
Oh, don't be so naive.
她完全可能继续回来要钱
She would have just come back for more.
治安官 没私下见过你最爱的两位演员吧
Hey, Sheriff. Never meet your heroes, right?
你花了那么多年策划杀掉自己的老婆
Kathleen: You spend years planning your wife's murder
结果被一个该死的临时演员敲诈
to get shafted by a fucking day player.
有必要的话我塞也要
I will shove that peanut butter
把花生酱塞进那小婊子的喉咙里
down that Juilliard bitch's throat if I have to.
不 听着 到此为止了
No. Okay, look, that's it.
我们要给她付钱
We're going to pay her off, alright.
我去联系我的经理
I'm going to call my business manager.
他肯定会暴怒的
He is going to have a fit.
迈克 这他妈是什么
Kathleen: Michael, what the fuck is that?
什么啊
Michael: What?
搞什么
What in the hell?
靠
Oh...shit.
我们完蛋了
We're fucked.
他们都听到了
They heard everything.
我现在该怎么办
What do I do now?
利用它
We use it.
该上场了 宝贝
Showtime, baby.
我以前每年都会等着那次游行
I used to wait for that parade every year.
独立日
Independence Day.
为了谁 为了什么
For who? From what?
鲍比的生父坠落在了日本海
Bobby's real daddy went down over the Sea of Japan.
1952年7月12日
July 12th, 1952.
他是个飞行员
An aviator.
你为什么选择了鲍比
Why did you take Bobby?
他哪儿都比我强
He was better than me in every way!
彭萨科拉的那年冬天很冷
Kathleen: It was cold in Pensacola that winter.
冷得不自然
Unnatural cold.
来得太早的霜
Frost that comes too early
迟迟不肯离去
means to stay too long,
可能永远不会离去
maybe forever.
雾气升起
The mists rise up.
遮盖住你的脚面 然后到腰
They cover your ankles, then your waist.
海洋想要延伸到云端
The sea longs to reach the clouds.
母亲和孩子伸出手寻找彼此
Mother and child reachin' out for each other.
我可爱的鲍比起飞的时候
When my sweet Bobby went up
总是会带着我
he always took me with him.
所以那一天
And so it follows that that day,
我也一起坠亡
I, too, went down.
那个寒冷的冬天
That cold winter.
这个冬天
This winter.
高至眼睫的雾气
The mists up to the lashline.
羽翼上的冰就是地上的雾气
Ice on the wing is mist on the ground,
是眼汨
is tears.
雾气升起
The mist rises up,
我跪下来迎接它
and I kneel down to meet it.
所以现在 我也
And so now I too become
变成了另一个彭萨科拉的
just another ghost.
幽灵
of Pensacola.
好
Man: Bravo!
我只是
*I'mjust*
百老汇新人
*A Broadway Baby*
拖着疲惫的步子
*Walking off my tired feet*
走在42街上
*Pounding 42nd Street*
为了参演
*To be in a show*
百老汇新人
*Broadway Baby*
学习如何唱如何跳
*Learning how to sing and dance*
等待着一举成名的机会
*Waiting for that one big chance*
参与演出
*To be in a show*